stevespanglerscience.com 2004-06-07

# Privacy and Security Policies - Steve Spangler Science

[All About Air](http://www.stevespanglerscience.com/category/25/) [Books & Resources](http://www.stevespanglerscience.com/category/2/) [Chemistry](http://www.stevespanglerscience.com/category/3/) [Color](http://www.stevespanglerscience.com/category/5/) [Crystals](http://www.stevespanglerscience.com/category/7/) [Density](http://www.stevespanglerscience.com/category/8/) [Electricity](http://www.stevespanglerscience.com/category/10/) [Energy](http://www.stevespanglerscience.com/category/11/) [Force & Motion](http://www.stevespanglerscience.com/category/12/) [Lab Supplies](http://www.stevespanglerscience.com/category/6/) [Light & Sound](http://www.stevespanglerscience.com/category/14/) [Magnetism](http://www.stevespanglerscience.com/category/15/) [Science Fair](http://www.stevespanglerscience.com/category/28/) [Science Toys](http://www.stevespanglerscience.com/category/4/) [Solar Science](http://www.stevespanglerscience.com/category/19/) [Weather](http://www.stevespanglerscience.com/category/9/) [Insects](http://www.stevespanglerscience.com/category/13/) [Plants](http://www.stevespanglerscience.com/category/17/) | | shopping cart  
---|---  
  
Welcome guest

Ready & waiting.

Log In Create Account | departments  
---|---  

|  Home > Help And FAQ >

Any personal information you provide to Steve Spangler Science will only be used to notify you of Steve Spangler Science news, services and activities. Steve Spangler Science will hold the information securely and will not disclose it except for this purpose or when required by law. You have the right to inspect and update your details at any time. If you do not wish to hear from us any longer, please email us at [info@stevespanglerscience.com](mailto:info@stevespanglerscience.com).

Steve Spangler Science is strongly committed to protecting your privacy and the security of your personal information. We use the information we collect to service your orders and to make improvements to our web site. Please review the following policy information to learn how Steve Spangler Science protects your personal information. If you have any questions, contact us at [info@stevespanglerscience.com](mailto:info@stevespanglerscience.com). 

**How does Steve Spangler Science protect customer information?**   
When you place an order with Steve Spangler Science through the web site, your information is transmitted over a secure server. Your online transactions with Steve Spangler Science automatically take place on a secure server. All information is encrypted before it is transmitted using SSL technology. Once your credit card is processed we do not retain your credit card number, an added measure of security for your credit information. 

**[](https://digitalid.verisign.com/as2/0532bb69d80459347d02f71ea089fa91) What information is being collected?**   
When you browse the Steve Spangler Science web site you do so anonymously. When you order we need to know your name, email address, mailing address, credit card number and expiry date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status. 

We do not collect personal or business information on Steve Spangler Science visitors unless it is voluntarily provided. Steve Spangler Science, to gain a better understanding of products and the services our customers are interested in, may use any information collected from you with your permission. We use this information to help us serve you better.

We may use this information to occasionally notify you about updates to Steve Spangler Science. If you wish to be removed from our mailing list, please email us at [info@stevespanglerscience.com](mailto:info@stevespanglerscience.com).

**What about the privacy of my personal information? Will the information be sold to third parties?**   
We will not sell, trade, rent, or give individually identifying information to third parties without your permission. Steve Spangler Science uses the personal information collected from you in the order process to help us deliver your order, to contact you about your order if we have questions, and to improve our site to serve you better. 

**Will I receive unsolicited e-mail from Steve Spangler Science?**   
Steve Spangler Science will send e-mail confirmation of all orders to our customers. From time to time we may contact our customers by e-mail with a newsletter and information about updates to our site. If you would like to receive e-mail updates from us, please check the appropriate box on the order form. 

Still uncomfortable ordering online? If you prefer not to order online you may order by phone, (800) 223-9080 from 8.00 AM to 5:00 PM, Monday through Friday. After these hours, please leave us a message and we will phone you the next business day to take your order and answer your questions. 

See also:

  * Shipping/Freight
  * Returns Policy
  * Terms and Conditions

**< Back to previous page**

|
